export const footballQuestions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    questionText: "With 260 goals, who is the Premier League's all-time top scorer?",
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Erling Haaland',
      optionTwo: 'Wayne Rooney',
      optionThree: 'Alan Shearer',
      optionFour: 'Robin Van Persie'
    },
    answer: 'Alan Shearer'
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    questionText: 'Which team won the first Premier League title?',
    answerOptions: [
      { answerText: 'Manchester United', isCorrect: true },
      { answerText: 'Nottingham Forest', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'Bolton Wanderers', isCorrect: false },
      { answerText: 'Newcastle United', isCorrect: false },
    ],
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Manchester United',
      optionTwo: 'Nottingham Forest',
      optionThree: 'Bolton Wanderers',
      optionFour: 'Newcastle United'
    },
    answer: 'Manchester United'
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    questionText: 'Which country has won the most World Cups?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'France',
      optionTwo: 'Argentina',
      optionThree: 'Germany',
      optionFour: 'Brazil'
    },
    answer: 'Brazil'
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    questionText: 'Which country has appeared in three World Cup finals, but never won the competition?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Portugal',
      optionTwo: 'Belgium',
      optionThree: 'Netherlands',
      optionFour: 'England'
    },
    answer: 'Netherlands'
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    questionText: 'The record number of World Cup goals is 16, scored by who?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Thomas Muller',
      optionTwo: 'Lionel Messi',
      optionThree: 'Ronaldo R9',
      optionFour: 'Miroslav Klose'
    },
    answer: 'Miroslav Klose'
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    questionText: 'Messi began his professional career at Barcelona, but what was his schoolboy team?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Boca Juniors',
      optionTwo: "Newell's Old Boys",
      optionThree: 'Young Boys',
      optionFour: 'La Masia'
    },
    answer: "Newell's Old Boys"
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    questionText: 'Who is the only player to win the Champions League with three different clubs?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Clarence Seedorf',
      optionTwo: 'Cristiano Ronaldo',
      optionThree: 'Zinedine Zidane',
      optionFour: 'Carlo Ancelotti'
    },
    answer: 'Clarence Seedorf'
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    questionText: 'With 365 goals, who holds the record for top Bundesliga goalscorer of all time?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Robert Lewandowski',
      optionTwo: 'Gerd Muller',
      optionThree: 'Miroslav Klose',
      optionFour: 'Erling Haaland'
    },
    answer: 'Gerd Muller'
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    questionText: "I have played for Chelsea and spent time playing in Turkey. I've been crowned African Footballer of the Year four times and the Africa Cup of Nations twice.Who am I?",
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Mikel Obi',
      optionTwo: 'Michael Essien',
      optionThree: 'Samuel Etoo',
      optionFour: 'Didier Drogba'
    },
    answer: 'Samuel Etoo'
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    questionText: "Which club is associated with 'Galacticos'?",
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Barcelona',
      optionTwo: 'Real Madrid',
      optionThree: 'Galatasaray',
      optionFour: 'Borussia Dortmund'
    },
    answer: 'Real Madrid'
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    questionText: 'In how many seasons has Messi finished the Champions League top scorer?',
    options: {
      optionOne: '4',
      optionTwo: '2',
      optionThree: '6',
      optionFour: '1'
    },
    answer: '6'
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    questionText: 'Manchester United overcame a 2-0 first-leg defeat to beat Olympiakos and reach the quarter-finals in 2014. Who scored his first Champions League hat-trick to make it happen?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Wayne Rooney',
      optionTwo: 'Danny Welbeck',
      optionThree: 'Angel Di Maria',
      optionFour: 'Robin Van Persie'
    },
    answer: 'Robin Van Persie'
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    questionText: 'Which of these clubs have never played in the Premier League?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Oldham',
      optionTwo: 'Barnsley',
      optionThree: 'Plymouth',
      optionFour: 'Blackpool'
    },
    answer: 'Plymouth'
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    questionText: 'With 162 in total, which player has the most Premier League assists?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Ryan Giggs',
      optionTwo: 'Mesut Ozil',
      optionThree: 'Steven Gerrard',
      optionFour: 'Frank Lampard'
    },
    answer: 'Ryan Giggs'
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    questionText: 'Which player scored the fastest Premier League hat-trick with 2 minutes and 57 seconds?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Cristiano Ronaldo',
      optionTwo: 'Harry Kane',
      optionThree: 'Erling Haaland',
      optionFour: 'Sadio Mane'
    },
    answer: 'Sadio Mane'
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    questionText: 'Which other player have scored the most headed goals in Premier League history alongside Peter Crouch?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Cristiano Ronaldo',
      optionTwo: 'Harry Kane',
      optionThree: 'Robin Van Persie',
      optionFour: 'Alan Shearer'
    },
    answer: 'Harry Kane'
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    questionText: 'Which African nation has gone furthest at the World Cup?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Ghana',
      optionTwo: 'Senegal',
      optionThree: 'Morocco',
      optionFour: 'Ivory Coast'
    },
    answer: 'Morocco'
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    questionText: 'Which player has the longest scoring runs in premier League history?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Ruud Van Nistelrooy',
      optionTwo: 'Jamie Vardy',
      optionThree: 'Harry Kane',
      optionFour: 'Alexandar Isak'
    },
    answer: 'Jamie Vardy'
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    questionText: 'Which player has the most free kick goals of all time?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Juninho',
      optionTwo: 'David Beckham',
      optionThree: 'Lionel Messi',
      optionFour: 'Rivaldo'
    },
    answer: 'Juninho'
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    questionText: 'Who broke the Champions League all-time record held by Raul Gonzalez at 71 goals?',
    options: {
      optionOne: 'Cristiano Ronaldo',
      optionTwo: 'Lionel Messi',
      optionThree: 'Zlatan Ibrahimovic',
      optionFour: 'Ronaldo R9'
    },
    answer: 'Lionel Messi'
  }
];